{
    "id": "4d2ce6fe15af49d2b6a56ff497fbd714",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He died so that he .................................. save his country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "776761092a1e4bf8bffefa573cdc831a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat so that we ..................................... live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "62d9abd0a9ea4c8ca9f41f8325fe3689"
        },
        {
            "question": "You .......................................... go only if you have permission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0c1218b11b6d456abb6a5fb8fcd24bec"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was so tired that he ...................................... hardly stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "679ca84a87e34d599a977f6a0ea26570"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to England in order that he .................................. become a barrister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "must",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2904bb936d514e778e27391b3dceff77"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ................................... do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c18b197ed804c5999f3d48bab8cd460"
        },
        {
            "question": "The robbers stole whatever they ..................................... find in the shop.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "may",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0f004fb194f4b5096d4c8121865d58b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard that he ..................................... win the prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "590afffe4b814e0596f3f87c5f64cb96"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ran so that we ..................................... arrive in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "could",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9ac76c07df0f41d1ae458245328e4c69"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ................................... try again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5d8534d3e8041c993911d348386eae2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran as quickly as he .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b1c6708776f4a558de08fd007ca304a"
        }
    ]
}